Akiyoi!
There wasn't any!
No, Punt Mike.
You'd do it just now.
That guy is so nervous.
Too nervous!
Akiyoshi!
We're close.
It's not a compliment.
I want you to come this way!
Go for it, Moeka!
I'll come to this kawaii
Akiyo-san's coming out!
Akiyo-san's leaving!
Oh!
Ooh!
Aah!
Photographer, do you have a chat?
Yes!
Give me some eyes over here!
When you've got them, look this way.
Yes, sir!
I'm a member.
Yes!
Now the three of you, over here.
Yes!Yes!!!
Too florid
Too flamboyant
So now we have three people here!
Yay!
Thank you very much!
I went to the dressing room and took them in.
I'm Sora Akane.
I'm Yuri Awa
I'm Yuukirina.
Yay!
I am Yuzuki Ishikawa
I'm Yuzuki
ana
Forgiven Speaker
me
thời oiest
allied
I am allied
I love you
Karaki Ai Putter
4 days
UMER r ah ah ah
Yin brother ne
Bye-bye.
With flowers, see each other.
OK? It's okay.
I can't help it.It can't be helped.
It can't be helped.
You two went out for fun, right?
Yes, yes.
I may or may not have knocked them down once.
Because Kojima was late.
That's right.
Talking about people.
You're making a daily mistake.
I'm not going to say it outright, but it left a mark.
That's a strong scar.
You've done a lot of pulling.
Well, that's great.
Did you get hit?
Oh, no?
Oh, my God?
How's it going?
Oh?
No, how's it going?
You got it? You like it?
How's it going? !
Nooooooo!
Nooooooooo!
We're not done yet.
It hasn't been hours.
I knew it... right there.
There it is.
I forgive you.
So... it's now one on one between Uka and Ameila, and the winner gets...
I'll take the winner of this one-on-one.Like I'm the one to one one.
You're the one.
So the loser has to listen to the other guy for a minute, okay?
Then let's move on to the next demonstration!
I'm left!
I'm closing in on my seniors.
I'll do it soon.
Almost there.
Yes!
I'm scared.
Scary.
Up you go!
Up!
Scream, Scream, Scream!
Yay! - Yay! - Yay!
Yeah!
One for one!
So long!
Oh, my God.
That's hot.
Ha-ha-ha!
And now, Sta-zakura and Yuzuki are here.
Oh!
There's a cute girl looking at me.There's a pretty little girl watching us.
Come here. Come here.
The cheerleader.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
He's so cute.
And the cheerleaders.
I heard they're really strong.
Punching?
More like a punching machine. She weighed 144 kilograms.
You have a pretty face.
Have you wrestled before?
I won a competition with an idol.
Wow!
She's good.
If I see her dance to the new song today, I think she'll beat me.
Yay!
Thank you.
It's not like dancing.
We have our own yokozuna.
They didn't say it was me, but I think it might be me.
We have a yokozuna.
Yokozuna doesn't carry much weight.
He's carrying the yokozuna on his back.
This is scary
That's good.
Yokozuna.
Mr. Seta.
Who are you two rooting for? Who are you two rooting for?
Chanchan.
But...
You're so kind.
Can I ask you to change your position?
Sure.
Castle of the castle
Yuzuki from the castle
We're already starting to make love.
I'm so excited.
We're not all in the same group, are we?
I think we're all on the same side, one by one.
You're so sweet.
Sorry, no hands.
Here we go.
Rabot.
I'm starting to feel more comfortable.
What do we got?
What's coming out?
Merry loop.
What do you got?
What's coming out?
They're playing nice.
Go, go, go, go! Push, push, push!
Go, go, go, go!
Push, push, push, push!
Spurion!
Freak!
Go, go, go, go!Go, go, go, go!
That feels good!
Is this not a win or something?
Do!
Yeah!
I got it!
Oh, my God!
That's great!
So, the winner is Sakuraki Seta!
You did it!
Do you have any requests for me?
Oh, when I say it, I'll say it in Hakata dialect.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no! There it is!
I heard you.
Are you really free?
I'll be watching from over here.
You're crazy!
Please, I have to ask you.
Oh, well, point it at Chanseitai.
Point it at the camera already.
I can hear you!
Whoa!
Is it bad?
That's great!
That's not a very nice thing to say.
No, it's a compliment.
I mean it in a good way.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, thank God!Oh, good!
I want to do it.
I'd love to do it.
Oh, you want to do it on top of that?
I'll do it on top of the senior.
You don't want to do it?
No, you want to push or be pushed?
What?
Push?
I can handle a push.
In the pool.
In the pool! I want to be pushed!
Mr. Tajima.
Well, I worked hard today.
I worked hard today.
What do you want to be told?
Hmm?
Anything?
Anything.
Well, then...
Mizuki...
Mizuki is the cutest.
Wow!
Put your heart into it.
Be sure.
First today, I'll go first.
Please.
You're the cutest, Yatsuki.
I love you so much!
Yay!Yay!
Me too.
We're done.
I'll leave you two alone.
I'll leave you two alone. I'm going to break up the party, too.
So, that was a push sumo.
Thank you very much.
Well, I'll see you two later.
One more time.
It's okay.
You.
Do it to me.
I'm so sorry.
I'll make sure to put a face on it, you.
Yatsuki might want to see it.
Really?
Turn around.
You're scaring me.
Your eyes are scary.
They're serious.
What can you tell me?
Are you sure?
You're the cutest thing I've ever seen, Dad.
I think I'm gonna wake up a little bit.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Look, look, look.
Hey, you.you (formerly honorific, now sometimes derog. term referring to an equal or inferior)
You.
I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared.
I'm scared
What's with that guy?
Thank you
Yay!
Yay! Yay!
So, what's next?
Yuzu and Hana no Ano guess
Yuzu and Hana-no-Anata's senpai came to see us!
Yay!
She's really beautiful!
Isn't she a beauty? That's...
Oh, my God!
What are you talking about?
I'm really pushing for it.
Really?
You're not getting it.
Whenever Momoko-san performs.
You always separate your faces a little.
Neri-chan is the favorite of both of us.
Anyway, I'm just going to be on the mic.
Really?
I get a bad mustache every time.
I appreciate it.Well, thank you so much!
I really love it.
Thank you.
So which one is it?
No, no, no, no, no.
About 30,000?
I have more of Takagi-san's stuff than you.
But I was pushing Momoko-san first.
But I...
I look at Neri's Instagram every day and worship her.
Oh, vs.
But I...
Neri-chan once gave me a hug
But Yuko too
I've danced with her at a labor event
Me too
I'm adjusting all my strength
Oh man, that's so uncool!
There's something about the experience
It's not like I'm a male or anything.
It's not what you have to do, it's what you have to do.
Okay, okay.
I'll give you a quiz.
And you answered correctly.
Neri's is better.
Neri-chan's quiz.
If I were you, I'd know.
May I?
That's it!
What will I dress up as this Halloween?What will I dress up as this Halloween?
Oh, my God.
I know great.
What will you dress up as?
Are you saying, Yuko?
I know.
At this point, you're out.
It's related to something I've been into lately.
I have to look at Instagram.
I have to look at my Instagram.
I'm looking.
And the hits are
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Shush, shush, shush, shush.
Ooh.
You know what I'm saying?
All right, let's see if we can get a couple of answers out of you.
That's enough.
What?
Se-no.
Ninja.
That's right.
Wow.
Two answers.
Thumb
Wrist
Wrist.
Wrist.Wrist
Wrist
wrist
ng
ه
Wait, weak.
You're good. You're good.
Chan chan.
Face.
The flowers are amazing.
You have a face that can't be shown to the world.
So, I won.
Thank you very much.
Yuuka, a favor.
Uh, yes. Contact, Yuuka. Contact? Can I please go through your office?
Oh, no! No, wait a minute.
Well, let me put you through to Kyuushi's, then to Airin's.
Can I put her through? Okay, okay.
Okay, then, go ahead and show it up. Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Here are the close-ups. Here it is.
Pushing sumo, cheering for demonstration, and remaining!
Up is up. Good, good, good.
Oh no. No, I can't do it. I'm going to throw up. I'm so nervous.
I get all teary-eyed when I see Kanako in front of me.
I'll win too. I want to win every game. I'll do my best. I'll do my best.Do I want to win too? Me, I want to win every game. I will do my best. I'll do my best.
Okay, I'll do my best.